<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Blog Name</title>
  <subtitle>Blog subtitle</subtitle>
  <id>http://blog.url.com/</id>
  <link href="http://blog.url.com/"/>
  <link href="http://blog.url.com/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
  <updated>2011-11-19T11:00:00-05:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Blog Author</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>The ten tango commandments</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/post/2011/11/top-ten-commandments/"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/post/2011/11/top-ten-commandments/</id>
    <published>2011-11-19T11:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2018-04-03T17:25:30-04:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Everything as fundamental to life as tango needs a moral code...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;transcript&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have you lost your way in this world?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This big world or tango which leaves so many of us with existential
unanswered questions:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Who am I?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why can&amp;#39;t I walk like Sebastian Achaval?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Do I really have an axis?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Should I be going to an advanced workshop after eight weeks of learning
tango?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why do I look like a 10 year old hanging from a supermarket trolley
whenever I attempt to Colgada?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;And what on earth is a Colgada in the first place?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fear not my brother.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My name is Kurt.
I am your local tango evangelist and I have got some answers for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My ten tango commandments are all you need for a life of bliss and
happiness for the rest of your dancing days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now lean back and listen well:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;First commandment&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tango and tango alone is your God.
Don&amp;#39;t even think about mentioning salsa or swing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Second commandment&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thou shalt not put moving images of yourself practising tango on YouTube.
They may be used against you when you have long forgotten about them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Third commandment&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thou shalt not use the name of tango in vain --
especially not in association with anything remotely resembling
fishnet stockings, roses, ballroom dancing, or Antonio Banderas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Fourth commandment&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remember the Sabbath.
Six days of tango per week are quite enough.
There is another form of life out there, in case you forgot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Fifth commandment&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thou shalt honor your father and your mother.
Spare them from the trauma of listening to your tales of perfect
tandas and the chemistry of a good embrace.
They wouldn&amp;#39;t understand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Sixth commandment&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thou shalt not murder.
Ladies, keep the control flows on the floor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Seventh commandment&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thou shalt not commit adultery.
Resist the temptation that all those smiles, compliments, and
tender embraces in the tango world seem to suggest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Eighth commandment&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thou shalt not steal teacher&amp;#39;s moves from the internet.
He looks cool doing them; you will look like an idiot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Ninth commandment&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thou shalt not bear false witness.
Cut down on the insincere compliments,
but if you have to bitch about everyone on the dance floor,
at least do it discreetly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Tenth commandment&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thou shalt not covet your neighbor&amp;#39;s instructional DVD,
your DJ&amp;#39;s new Canaro CD, or your teacher&amp;#39;s black and white
tango shoes -- get your own.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Tango truths: why men dance and women sit</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/post/2011/10/why-man-dance-woman-sit/"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/post/2011/10/why-man-dance-woman-sit/</id>
    <published>2011-10-28T12:00:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2018-04-03T18:54:55-04:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Just another night at a big city milonga&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;transcript&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: Hey man, good to see you.
How are things?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;B: All good, thanks.  And yourself?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: Couldn&amp;#39;t be better.
The work is done for the week and now it&amp;#39;s tango
all night long.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;B: Look at all those gorgeous followers sitting over there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: Amazing!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;B: Awesome.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: There is a new lady too.  Have you seen her before?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;B: Never, but I heard she is from Detroit.
You should dance with her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: I should, but I&amp;#39;ll wait until I have seen her dance.
Better safe than sorry.  Why don&amp;#39;t you ask her first?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;B: I should, but I had to work through my virtual
favorites list: DiSarli with Jessica, D&amp;#39;Arienzo with
Francesca,  a vals tanda with Jill.
I am booked for an hour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: I know, mate, it&amp;#39;s tough being a guy.
If I don&amp;#39;t dance with my usual ladies, I get the nasty
looks next milonga.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(&lt;em&gt;one hour later&lt;/em&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: How is the list going?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;B: I am through most of my compulsory dances.
Look at this: the new lady still hasn&amp;#39;t danced yet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: That&amp;#39;s horrible.
Poor lady, she probably traveled for hours to get here.
You should ask her for a dance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;B: I should, but it&amp;#39;s a milonga tanda.
That&amp;#39;s never a good set to start with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: I agree.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(&lt;em&gt;A new girl enters&lt;/em&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: Holy jesus!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;B: God almighty!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: Who is this? Look at those legs,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;B: And the long hair.
She can&amp;#39;t be older than 25, and the skirt hardly
covers her bum.
Tasteless, but why not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: Look! The way she just smiled at me.
I have no idea who she is, but I will dance
with her right now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;B: She was clearly looking at me,
so excuse me momentarily.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(&lt;em&gt;one hour later&lt;/em&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;B: Wow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: Huh? That was hard work.
I followed her around for an hour to be in a good position
for a cabeceo but it worked in the end.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;B: Tell me about it.
It seems all the men have gone bonkers all of a sudden.
How was it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: Her dancing is rubbish.
But with those legs, who cares?
She is hot, I tell you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;B: Look, our lady from Detroit still hasn&amp;#39;t danced.
That&amp;#39;s criminal. Why don&amp;#39;t you dance with her?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: I should, but this is Troilo playing,
it&amp;#39;s really not my cup of tea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;B: Fair enough.
It&amp;#39;s not my favorite either.
Oh excuse me, I think I just got a cabeceo from Kelly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(&lt;em&gt;one hour later. La Cumparsita. last tanda.&lt;/em&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;B: Wow, the evening went fast.
It&amp;#39;s hard work keeping the ladies happy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: I hear you.
We selflessly give away our tango gift for the greater good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;B: Did you notice: the lady from Detroit finally danced
a tanda?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: Yes. With Floyd the furniture mover.
Not exactly the stuff tango dreams are made of.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;B: Poor lady. She actually dances very nicely.
She deserves better than that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: Yes. Floyd told me that she is a tango teacher.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;B: that tango teacher?
Bloody Floyd!
Couldn&amp;#39;t he have asked her for a dance earlier?&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>The loneliness of the long dancing milonguera</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/post/2011/09/loneliness-long-milonguera/"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/post/2011/09/loneliness-long-milonguera/</id>
    <published>2011-09-12T12:00:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2018-04-23T11:09:42-04:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;For all those on a quest for tango perfection!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;transcript&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: Priscila, you are my hero!
From the first time I saw you, I admired you on the
dance floor -- your grace, your elegance,
your posture, the way you walk.
You are my tango ????.
Your adornos have the graceful touch of a butterfly.
Your boleos are sharp as a Swiss Army knife.
Men line up to get a dance with you.
Priscilla, I want to dance like you.
Show me how to achieve happiness through tango!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Priscilla: Happiness? What makes you think the tango
is the way to happiness?
What could I give to be in your shoes once again --
not the junky tango clogs you are wearing,
but metaphorically speaking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: I began tango just a year ago.
I was an average middle-class intellectual with a
PhD in continental philosophy, and a burning desire for
self-fulfillment.
I have since divested myself of worldly matters:
the education of my kids,
the well-being of my husband,
and my friends.
In the big picture of the universe, they matter little.
But I need to sort out those boleos.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;P: You are on the quest for perfection?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: Utter perfection.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;P: Show them ???&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: ???&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;P: Desperate Housewives have shown us that ambition
in the pursuit of perfection is a slippery slope.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: Where else but in tango can we feel so
beautiful as we strive for perfection?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;P: Let me give you a reality check, darling.
I have danced with the best dancers in the world.
I have experienced perfection.
Everything that follows is a disappointment.
These days I enter a milonga and I witness the shrill
cacophony of bodies consulting each
other at the worst possible moment in the music.
I see otherwise respectable middle-aged people
entangling their lower bodies as if they had been
studying the Kama Sutra.
And strong emetic reflexes take hold of me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: But who cares about them?
You are the best dancer in town --
who would not want to be like you?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;P: Nobody, darling, nobody.
I have spent countless hours perfecting my dance with
the best teachers.
I spent most of my yearly income on tango --
and what for?
Now I see abject misery once I set foot through the door.
It&amp;#39;s like walking through the streets of Dickensian London.
Bad posture, bad balance, bad centre,
bad musicality, bad floor craft,
lack of dynamics, of variation, and subtlety in the dance.
I see the seedy underbelly of tango wherever I go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: But you are a tango VIP.
You get first class treatment wherever you go.
Dancers will travel for hours if you announce your
arrival on Facebook.
While I only get dances with bottom-feeders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;P: Tango is a game of diminishing returns, darling.
First you dance with everyone who comes up to you.
Then you prefer to dance with 3 or 4 people in your city.
Then you go to the next bigger city, until you end up
with another three or four people.
Not for me.
Unless I cross oceans for a dance
and travel to the other side of the world,
I cannot motivate myself to go out of the house.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: You are not suggesting I become a Sunday afternoon
tea and cookie dancer?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;P: You are the philosopher.
Schopenhauer knew that
your ambition for tango perfection was futile.
He knew that you would never be as good as the
YouTube stars you admire.
Tango ambition will only lead to loneliness and bitterness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: Priscilla, what am I to do?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;P: Get a cat, or a hunky lover.
Or moved to Buenos Aires.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Facebook envy -- a tango perspective</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/post/2011/05/facebook-envy/"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/post/2011/05/facebook-envy/</id>
    <published>2011-05-19T12:00:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2018-04-04T08:58:34-04:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Following the daily updates on the exploits of our
dear tango friends fills us with joy and happiness!
Or does it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;transcript&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why am I here, when everybody else has gone home?
Why do I have to prepare this stupid portfolio for
tomorrow when I could be dancing tango?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, there is a new message for me on Facebook.
Let&amp;#39;s take a look. What is Sharon writing here?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;I am having a great time at Nora&amp;#39;s tango week.
Tango dancing doesn&amp;#39;t get any better than this.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I see. And what is this? &amp;quot;Elton loves milongas in
New York&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;So many good followers.
Murat and Michelle were amazing.
Have been going to bed at 5am every morning.
I am in tango heaven.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gosh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is it with those tango people?
Do they not have a real life?
Why am I sitting here at work when all these
people are enjoying themselves?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This one is from Priscilla.  Of course she is in
Buenos Aires -- where else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She says: &amp;quot;Oh my god!
Francisco danced three tandas in a row with me,
last night at Practica X.
You all know what this means, smiley face.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have no idea what it means, but I don&amp;#39;t care.
Tango blasphemy means swapping your life,
a successful active professional woman, for that of a
smiling, subordinate, follower who gratefully receives
the crumbs that the Priscilla&amp;#39;s of this world leave
behind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ah, and here is Kurt.
Obviously Kurt never really wanted me, not for tango anyway.
Of course I was stupid enough to fall for a tango alpha male.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is he writing?
Kurt&amp;#39;s schedule for the next three weeks --
Berlin tango festival,
Capri tango festival,
Syracuse tango festival,
Montreal tango festival.
Disgusting!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where do these people get their holidays from?
Who pays them all the money to jet set around the world
and dance tango?
Do they not work? Do they not have to go shopping,
do the washing, and bring the kids to school?
Do they not have to pay off a mortgage?
And why am I here filing tax returns?
I hate my life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This message is from Enrique Blanco, or Henry White as
he was known before he started tango.
He too is in Buenos Aires.
My god, is there no other destination on earth?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He writes: &amp;quot;Have just completed a one-week seminar with
Gustavo Naveira.  He has taken my tango to a whole new
level!&amp;quot;
Ah, and here he is in a picture arm-in-arm with his
teacher, smiling at the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bastard! Perfect boleo.  Perfect milongas.
Perfect dancers. Perfectly nimble bodies and
perfect teachers everywhere.
It&amp;#39;s like living in Wisteria Lane!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My boleos suck. My bum looks big in everything.
I don&amp;#39;t call any famous tango dancer my friend.
Javier Rodriguez has never hugged me.
What&amp;#39;s worse my tango teacher is about as inspiring as a
tax auditor.
What is wrong with me?
Where do I find the shiny tango glamour world?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe tango happiness comes only to those who seek it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What shall we write? Okay!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;I am having an awesome time at the Barcelona tango
festival!
Last night I danced 3 tandas with... erm...
how shall we call him?
Three tenders with Lorenzo...
You all know what that means...
Smiley face.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or maybe I should simply delete my Facebook account.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>How authentic is your tango?</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/post/2011/05/how-authentic-tango/"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/post/2011/05/how-authentic-tango/</id>
    <published>2011-05-06T12:00:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2018-04-23T09:53:29-04:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;As you would expect from a religion, tango heaven
awaits those who follow the traditions.
As for the rest - your local tango High Priest is
watching you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;transcript&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Krupke: Hey you! Yes I mean you, punk.
I have been meaning to have a word with you for
a long time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anton: Hey Mr. Krupke. My name is Anton.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;K: I don&amp;#39;t care what your name is.
But I know that you are one of those tango nuevo punks
who have been sabotaging this milonga lately.
This used to be a beautiful place, here at the west side
milonga -- traditional tango music, discreet and
well-dressed people, decorum on the dance floor --
and then you lot came along.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: And what happened?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;K: People with dreadlocks, beards, and baggy trousers
started appearing.
They are asking for ridiculous music, and they are
dancing boleos and gachos as if they were auditioning for
Cirque du Soleil.  It&amp;#39;s like a social disease.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: I am not sure that I can follow you.
What is the problem with that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;K: The problem is that is has nothing to do with
authentic tango.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: Can you define authentic tango for me?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;K: Yes. Authentic tango is tango as it was danced in
Buenos Aires during the Golden Age, in the 1930s and 1940s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: So you were declaring that tango is dead?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;K: We are trying to preserve true tango against delinquents
like yourself.
You punks have no respect --
women dancing with women,
men dancing with men. It&amp;#39;s like a whorehouse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: Of course none of these things ever featured in the
history of tango...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;K: You punk just need some respect for the traditions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: So you think just because you put on a suit,
play a song from the 1940s, and call your shuffling
milonguero style, you are preserving tango?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;K: The dancers back then surely did not look like
terrorists on the run.
And they did not dance to Tom Waits either.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: The dancers back then surely did not arrive at the
milonga in a BMW convertible wearing a $2,000 Armani suit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;K: What are you saying?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: I am saying that dressing up like an Argentine when you
are not, and pretending that you understand the culture
when you have visited a few tourist circuits milongas in
Buenos Aires makes you about as authentically Argentinian
as a cheeseburger.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;K: I have been to Buenos Aires many times.
They know me by my first name at the Confiterial Ideal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: Yeah, that&amp;#39;s a prime location for authentic tango.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;K: At least I respect the traditions and the culture and
that&amp;#39;s a lot more than can be said for you, my friend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: Tradition.  All I hear is follow tradition.
Is this a religion or is it a dance?
And are you its law-enforcement officer?
Shouldn&amp;#39;t you be enjoying yourself as we are all trying
to enjoy ourselves?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;K: If you don&amp;#39;t follow the traditions of tango,
you will never understand the dance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: Oh really?
What will I not understand?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;K: The unspeakable sadness of tango poetry, for example.
Being dejected from society,
being poor, being without prospects in life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: Well mister Krupke, while you were busy understanding
the unspeakable sadness of tango poetry with your bad
Spanish, while you were trying very hard to look poor.
dejected, and without prospects in life,
will you excuse me momentarily.
I will invite a fellow punk for a Cirque du Soleil audition.
And by the way Mr. Krupke -- Krup you!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Tango versus Salsa</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/post/2011/04/tango-vs-salsa/"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/post/2011/04/tango-vs-salsa/</id>
    <published>2011-04-10T12:00:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2018-04-03T19:57:47-04:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;There is a good reason why these two exquisite dance forms
are usually kept well away from each other.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;transcript&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;T: Excuse me -- I was under the impression that there
was a milonga here tonight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;S: A what?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;T: A milonga -- you know, tango dancing?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;S: Oh no.
Thank God it&amp;#39;s Wednesday -- tonight is salsa night.
Tango was yesterday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;T: Oh no, I missed the tango.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;S: You should be glad. You look like you can do
with a few happy hormones anyway.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;T: Thank you, but salsa is really not my cup of tea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;S: Too much fun, right? I can always tell the difference.
A salsa dancer comes in the room and it&amp;#39;s like:
yay, let&amp;#39;s party.
A tango dancer comes in with a stone face and goes,
okay, this is so deep and meaningful, let&amp;#39;s be serious.
It&amp;#39;s like you are all craving depression.
Just imagine listening to music all night that goes on
about how crappy life is.
Salsa music on the other hand ...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;T: Salsa music on the other hand is invariably about a
conceited chauvinistic ass who thinks he is God&amp;#39;s gift
to women.
And while he sings about his poor Alma and Corazon, the
trumpets blow your ears off twice per minute in
celebration of his manliness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;S: Salsa is like a chick flick: good, predictable and
unadulterated fun.
Tango is like a pretentious Swedish art house movie:
nobody gets it, but if you don&amp;#39;t want to look stupid
afterwards, you pretend that you found it truly
intriguing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;T: That must be the reason why in salsa, conversations
start with &amp;#39;how are you&amp;#39; and they end with &amp;#39;good&amp;#39;.
Tango people at least have something to talk about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;S: Like their retirement funds, or their grandchildren?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;T: At least in tango you don&amp;#39;t have to fight off sleazebags
all night long, who want to give you private lessons, and
send you 50 text messages the next day saying how
beautiful you are.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;S: It is kind of cute.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;T: It&amp;#39;s tacky. Tango is like making love, salsa is
like having sex -- no subtlety.
I am a grown-up woman and not a teenager.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;S: What do you mean tacky?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;T: I am NOT looking at anyone. (&lt;em&gt;folds arms
and stare at B&amp;#39;s dress&lt;/em&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;S: Women in salsa look sexy.
Women in tango look like a sack of potatoes hanging
from the neck of a guy who could be their father.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;T: In ten years when you get your first wrinkles and the
saggy bum, the womanizing salsa gods you dance with
now will still seduce twenty year olds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;S: In ten years the men you dance with will be
spoon-fed by a nurse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;T: Oh my god. What is this?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;S: Ah, you are lucky -- they are dancing bachata tango.
Now you can show us your moves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;T: This has got to be a bad marketing ploy --
salsa people wanting to add some spice and passion with
a few ganchos? That&amp;#39;s almost as bad as Zumba.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;S: I love Zumba.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;T: One day they will even come up with a salsa version of
El Choclo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;S: Did you know that the corn cob in El Choclo is really
just a phallic symbol?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;T: Um no I did not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;S: Now is that tacky or what?
But don&amp;#39;t worry -- I am NOT looking at anyone.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
</feed>
